// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q027: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'The application deadline for the craft class is next Monday, so those interested should submit their paperwork as ------ as possible.',
      choices: ['quick', 'quicken', 'quickly', 'quickness'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['quickly'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ the congested traffic in the center of the city, we managed to make it to our client meeting on time.',
      choices: ['Despite', 'Although', 'Now that', 'In order that'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Despite'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Upon ------, materials on redevelopment projects in the Pura area can be made available to the public.',
      choices: ['duration', 'token', 'request', 'allowance'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['request'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Sapporo is the largest city in Hokkaido, ------ population is about 2 million and steadily increasing.',
      choices: ['its', 'which', 'their', 'whose'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['whose'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Materials ------ for painting classes must be purchased and prepared in advance.',
      choices: ['necessitate', 'necessary', 'necessity', 'necessarily'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['necessary'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Renowned consultant Emilio Gomez ------ will directly instruct participants in the marketing workshop.',
      choices: ['he', 'himself', 'his', 'him'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['himself'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'If it had not rained, the outdoor performances by local artists would not ------.',
      choices: ['postponed', 'have postponed', 'have been postponed', 'had been postponed'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['postponed'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ increasing the sales staff, we were able to improve sales by approximately 20% this year.',
      choices: ['Contrary to', 'On behalf of', 'As a result of', 'Regardless of'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['of'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Sratus Technology’s batteries sell well because they have a ------ lifespan than competing products.',
      choices: ['long', 'length', 'longest', 'longer'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['longer'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Greer Travel Agency specializes in planning trips ------ to each individual’s needs.',
      choices: ['tailoring', 'tailored', 'tailors', 'tailor'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['tailored'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}